Narrator: 16
Speaker: a bag
Narrator: 22
Speaker: a bank card
Narrator: 33
Speaker: a calendar
Narrator: 10
Speaker: a charger
Narrator: 13
Speaker: a coin
Narrator: 6
Speaker: a diary
Narrator: 25
Speaker: a dictionary
Narrator: 24
Speaker: earphones
Narrator: 2
Speaker: a file
Narrator: 4
Speaker: glasses
Narrator: 23
Speaker: headphones
Narrator: 14
Speaker: an identity card
Narrator: 12
Speaker: a key
Narrator: 31
Speaker: a lamp
Narrator: 3
Speaker: a laptop
Narrator: 18
Speaker: a magazine
Narrator: 30
Speaker: a mask
Narrator: 15
Speaker: a newspaper
Narrator: 32
Speaker: a notebook
Narrator: 28
Speaker: a pen
Narrator: 17
Speaker: a pencil
Narrator: 1
Speaker: a phone
Narrator: 9
Speaker: a photo
Narrator: 21
Speaker: a piece of paper
Narrator: 26
Speaker: a purse
Narrator: 20
Speaker: scissors
Narrator: 5
Speaker: sunglasses
Narrator: 27
Speaker: a tablet
Narrator: 29
Speaker: a ticket
Narrator: 8
Speaker: a tissue
Narrator: 11
Speaker: an umbrella
Narrator: 7
Speaker: a wallet
Narrator: 19
Speaker: a watch